sporttube.com 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy

or Log In with email address

Sign Up with Email

Email adress Incorect or no email!

Name Name field is required!

Password The password must be at least 6 characters long, must contain uppercase, lowercase letters and least one number. Wrong or no password!

Date of birth

In order to register you must be 18 or over.

Message

The account has been created successfully.

OK

SportTube will send you a notification whenever this match is updated.

Example notification

This is an example notification

SportTube.com

You can unsubscribe anytime

No thanks

Oops! It seems you have blocked notifications.

Please allow notifications from browser preferences to receive a notification.

OK

Embed video

The code has been copied to your clipboard.

OK

This video will be available in 9s.

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy - GDPR is an integral part of the Agreement about SportTube.com as set out in the provisions regarding processing of personal data in the Agreement about SportTube.com. 

The following Privacy Policy covers how any data directly or indirectly relates to the entity called the User in the Agreement (the "User") is handled and processed by SportTube.com (the "Website"), together referred to as the "Parties" and separately as a "Party". 

#### Lawful basis

In accordance with EU GDPR effective May 25th 2018 we follow the lawful basis of consent to collect and process the data described in this document. Each user on SportTube.com will be asked to give consent, allowing the Website to collect and process personal information related with privided features by SportTube.com. (for more information refer to: [http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN)) 

#### Collection of Personal Information

The Website does not collect any Personal Data when Users simply browse the Website. However, the Website does require that Users supply some Personal Data when using additional or advanced services provided on the Website after the registration. On these occasions the Website will ask Users for their respective consent prior to the collection and use of the User's Personal Data. Upon registration or at other times the Website may ask Users to submit their personal information. 

#### What and why we collect about you?

Name | Account name  
---|---  
Email | Used for in regards to: 

  * User authentication;
  * Send Users forgotten password to their respective personal account;
  * Send Users information which the Website thinks they will find useful, including information on new features, services information and commercial / advertising materials on offer by the Website / advertising materials on offer by third parties the Website cooperate with; 

Password | Used in regards to login. Encrypted  
Date of birth | To verify that User is over 18 years old.  
  
#### How we share information we collect?

The Website will never share any information with 3rd party without first notifying the User in order to obtain specific consent. The information is shared internally within the Website, but only to relevant people. This is done to ensure the User gets the best possible user experience. 

#### How we store and secure information we collect?

The Website have adopted various measures, both technical and organisational, to help protect against the destruction, loss, misuse and alteration of Personal Data which has been collected and used. Notwithstanding these efforts, the Website cannot guarantee that such event will not occur. The Personal Data is kept only for the time period required to meet the purposes for which it was collected. In case of user won't use the Website can request of account deleting. This can be done by submiting a request in the account profile settings. 

#### Other important privacy information

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files which a website may put on Your device when You first visit a site or page. The cookie will help the website, or another website, to recognise Your device the next time You visit. We use cookies to store your session info and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site analytics partners. See <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

**Emails**  
When you write to our support email, your message is stored in our ticket system. We store it so we can more easily see previous communication when you contact us. 

**Log Files**  
In order to better administer the Website and to collect broad demographic information of Visitors for aggregate use, the Website automatically logs the IP address of all Users and the pages viewed by each User respectively. 

**Site usage**  
Like many other sites, we use Google Analytics. Google Analytics helps us to analyze how our site is used. We do not use information specifically about you, we use statistics about the general usage of our site. 

Dated: May 2018

The site is using cookies to make your surfing easier.
